

CEPHAS OYIWOSE OSAYI

PROFILE

An independent and self-motivated computer science graduate with interest in Data. Experience working in an IT company as frontend engineer and in a Government establishment as a desk officer. Highly analytical, motivated and skilled at solving technical problems. Can work well both independently and in a team.

MY SKILLS

PROGRAMMING

WEB DESIGN

DIGITAL MARKETING AND ANALYTICS

DATA ANALYISIS

MICROSOFT OFFICE SKILLS

ORGANIZATION

COMMUNICATION

TEAMWORK

ADAPTABILITY

REFERENCE

On Request

Lafia, Nasarawa State.

080

08077827613

in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ceph asosayi/

WORK EXPERIENCE

cephasosayi@gmail.com

Front-end Developer Ullweb Technology

2021 - Present

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Maintaining brand consistency throughout the design.
- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones.
- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code

Web Designer Easydrop Web Services

2020- 2021

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Develop new user facing features
- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code

Desk Officer

Board of Internal Revenue Nasarawa State

2019- 2021

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Data Collection
- Tax Processing officer
- Payment invoice generation and payments.

EDUCATION HISTORY

B.sc Computer Science

2016 - 2021

Federal University Lafia

- Gained extensive training and successfully accomplished all courses for computer sciences
- Graduated with a second class honour degree

Front-end Career Path

Google/Andela Scholarship

2018

Digital Marketing

Google Garage

2019

Data Analyst

Codecademy Micro COurse

2019